本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译   米小勒    Lottie筱妤    CS小明漫画家    蔡茸茸   我叫魏碧慧
翻译   kiko    Marshal同学   天启章鱼X    小欠   小酸奶
时间轴   太太乐叽叽   浓子     后期   小亲斤
校对   米小勒      总监   米小勒
僵 尸
国 度
.
第一季 第五集
《僵尸国度》前情提要
Previously on Z Nation.
是活生生的宝宝
Whoa. It's a real live baby.
得像拿着点燃的手榴弹那样抱他  给我吧
You don't hold him like he's a live grenade. Just give him to me.
我对孩子没经验
Me and babies, not so much.
我们在执行高优先级任务
We're on a high priority mission
把这位先生送去加州的疾病控制中心研究所
to get this man to a CDC lab in California.
他无法去帮那些正在执行自杀任务的
He can't worry about some raggedy ass group of civilians
我们不是什么民间破烂蠢队  长官
Nothing raggedy ass about this group of civilians, sir.
放松
Relax,
加内特和沃伦心里有数
Garnett and Warren know what they're doing.
南伊利诺伊
给你的
There you are.
谢谢亲爱的
Ah, thank you, honey.
没什么比的上清晨的第一杯
Mmmm-mmm. Nothing like the first cup.
我跟你的维柯丁[止痛药]
I will see your vicodin
再加注一颗四环素
and raise you one tetracycline.
我跟
Call.
三同号[三张牌相同]
Three of a kind.
手中一组三张同点和一组两张同点的一共五张牌
满堂红
Full house.
最大点的哦
Aces high.
有没有搞错
Man.
你已经连赢五把牌了
That's five hands in a row.
如果你还想继续用老子的牌桌玩
If you're gonna continue to use my deck
就别再从屁股里面变牌出来了
you need to quit pulling cards out your ass.
矮油  矮油
Oh boo hoo.
嘘  等会再说  市民Z回来了
Hey shhh. Hold on, he's back on.
朋友们  我要告诉你们  恶劣天气即将来袭
Friends, I'm talking about mean weather coming in fast.
有报告说是龙卷风
Some reports of tornados.
快找个避难处躲躲吧
Find shelter and take cover.
现在在外待着  比以往都要更为危险
It's dangerous out there. More so than usual.
现在让我为大家放一曲灾难当前的暖人歌曲吧
Now back to the soothing sounds of the Apocalypse.
你知道吗  当他搞错了直升机的事儿后
You know after he was so wrong about that chopper
我现在觉得天气播报员的活儿挺适合他
weatherman's a pretty good job for that geek.
到你们了
You're up.
都还好吧
All good?
和谐的一晚
Peaceful night.
你的死忠粉刚才告诉我们将有暴雨来袭
Your stalker said there's a storm front coming in.
外面现在有迹象吗
How is it out there?
乌云当空  僵尸可能也会来
Cloudy with a chance of zombie.
好的  你们俩去休息吧
Okay, you two get some rest.
遵命
You got it.
我曾过过比这更糟的日子
I've had worse days.
这儿也算不上差了
It's not a bad set up.
你知道吗
You know,
我还真在这儿找到了家的感觉
I'm really starting to feel at home here.
我考虑之后在这搞个烤肉趴
I'm thinking about putting a barbecue right here.
这位先需要被打扫一下了
This one needs to be flipped.
我真的很喜欢屋主设计的景观  还有这花啊
I really like what they did with the landscaping, the flowers,
一切的一切  特有家的感觉
everything. So homey.
是啊  可惜他们都挂了
Yeah. Too bad they're dead.
抱歉了  走错屋子了
Sorry. Wrong room.
好了
Okay.
哇靠  还有床呢  上一次咱俩在床上做是哪年的事儿了
Oh my God. A bed. When was the last time we did it in a bed?
你怎么看
What do you think?
裸不
Naked?
你说衣服都脱了吗
Like no clothes?
必须一丝不挂  宝贝
Full commando, baby.
矮油  你还真是个多情滴种子
Oh my God, you are such a romantic.
这个...
The...
毯子...
blanket...
我只不过看到它...
I was just...
不好意思
Sorry.
那货真可怕
Scared of that one.
最好别去招惹她
Best not to mess.
要是咱们好好培养那两位
You know if we breed those two,
这些僵尸们都得完蛋了
it'd be all over for the zombies.
我记不起上次跟人偷偷溜出来是什么时候了
Can't remember the last time I snuck off with somebody.
我都记不起上次有这个念头是什么时候的事了
I can't remember the last time I wanted to.
你还在想他吗
You still think about him?
安托万吗
Antoine?
我试着不去想他
I try not to.
而且我也不知道后来发生了什么
And I never heard what happened,
所以其实没什么关系
so there's not much point.
你呢
What about you?
我之前每天都会想艾米和孩子们
I used to think about Amy and the kids everyday.
每次闭上眼睛  分别的情景就历历在目
Every time I closed my eyes, I saw the end all over again.
到了一定程度  我就放弃了
It got to a certain point where I just gave up.
不去在乎我到底是死是活了
Didn't care if I lived or died.
然后有趣的事情就发生了
And a funny thing happened.
我没有死
I didn't die.
发生了这么多事
And with everything that's happened
我已经越来越难以回想起从前的事了
it's been harder and harder to remember the past.
我猜这应该算是件好事吧  对吗
I guess that's a good thing, right?
应该吧
Guess so.
我们是不是离你的家乡很近了
Are we close by your hometown?
我知道你在想什么  我的回答是不行
I know what you're thinking, and the answer is no.
咱们往西走的时候顺路去一下就好
Just swing by on our way west.
为什么  都过去了
Why? It's long gone.
他已经不在了
He's gone.
我只希望我当时能等等他
And I just wish that I would've waited for him
能在我最后一次出发之前和他说声再见
and said goodbye before the last time I got shipped out.
你不想去确认一下吗
Don't you want to know for sure?
你自己都还不清楚的事情
You can't start forgetting
不能就这么开始忘记
what you don't know.
这看上去可不妙
That does not look good.
是龙卷风
It's tornado weather.
听起来就在耳边啊
That was close.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Uh, yeah.
不
No.
不  我不知道
No, I dunno.
他们过来了
Incoming!
阿猫阿狗们  咱得走了
Puppies and kittens! Time to go!
所有人从后门出去
Everybody out the back!
我助你脱离苦海
I give you mercy.
北极光
美国国安局作战指挥中心
搜索信号中
我讨厌通信盲点  伙计
I hate blind spots, boy.
让人家好紧张呢
Make me anxious.
紧张得消化不良了
Mess with my digestion.
真有趣
That was funny.
搜索信号中
不好意思  我忘了你了
Sorry, I forgot you.
对了  你在戒酒
Oh that's right, you're on the wagon.
对不起  我又忘了
Sorry, I forgot.
比自饮自酌更惨的就是滴酒不能沾了
The only thing worse than drinking alone is not drinking.
你好  美女
Hello, beautiful.
咱们要找什么呢
What are we looking at here?
厉害  龙卷风走廊果然名不虚传
Dang. They don't call it Tornado Alley for nothing.
我没醉
I am not drunk.
你才醉了
You're drunk.
你全家都醉了
No, your mom's drunk.
为了持续为您带来
In our continuing effort to bring you
最新消息  我们僵尸电视台调用了
up to the minute information, we at Z-TV have acquired
已被弃用多时的
a National Weather Service satellite
气象局卫星信号
that they aren't using anymore.
但这不是本次播报的重点
But that's not important.
现在镜头转向南方天气预报员约翰·史密斯
We now go to John Smith, southern weather correspondent
请他来谈谈最近的天气状况
to get his opinion on the story.
这可是我这老多年见过的最强的风暴
This is the badassest storm this weatherman has ever seen.
从墨西哥湾一直延伸到密西西比河谷
From the Gulf of Mexico right up the Mississippi Valley,
麻烦临头咧
trouble is brewing.
我不知道这玩意儿该叫飓风还是龙卷风
I don't know if they call this thing a turricane or a tornado
还是别的啥  但只要你呆在芝加哥南边
or what. But if you're anywhere south of Chicago
或者落基山脉东边
or east of the Rockies,
我可得警告你  赶紧躲起来吧
I'm issuing a get your butt in a bunker warning.
我希望你们几位能听到这个
Hey, I hope you guys are getting this.
艾迪和其他几位
Addy and friends.
你们得赶紧找地方躲起来  因为
You guys got to seek shelter immediately because
这场风暴特别强  还有
this is bad. And
你们去找藏身的地方
when you seek shelter immediately
找到之后
and after you do that,
请你们联系我  告诉我你们的位置
you need to contact me and tell me where you are.
我会告诉你们接下来该怎么做  好吗
And I'll update you with further instructions. Okay?
我是市民Z  本次播音完毕
All right, well this is Citizen Z, and I'm signing off.
艾迪是谁啊
Who's Addy?
我们往哪去
So which way do we go?
风暴从墨西哥湾向北推进
The storm is pushing north from the gulf.
如果我们能走上70号州际公路
If we make it to the I-70,
就能躲开风暴
we can outrun it.
这风暴可比那破烂卡车快多了
That storm is going faster than that craptastic truck ever will.
我们不能在大路上走了
Yeah, we got to get off the road.
你听见市民Z的建议了
You heard Citizen Z.
我们得赶紧找庇护所去
We got to seek shelter.
我们要做的是赶紧离开这里
What we need is to get the hell out of here.
我可不会就因为个卫星小子说两句话就不走了
I ain't stopping just cuz some punk with a satellite says so.
慢着  我听错了什么了吗
Okay, hang on. Am I missing something?
你们大老远把我拽过来
You did not drag my ass this far
可不是为了让龙卷风把人类救星吸上天吧
so that mankind's hope could get sucked up by a tornado,
是吧
did you?
艾迪
Hey, Addy.
你一直也不说个话
You know you've been quiet.
我就是问问你没事吧
Just want to make sure you're okay.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
就是
Just,
你懂的  都是僵尸惹的祸
you know, zombies.
谁给哥来颗薄荷糖呗
Anybody got a mint?
卡斯尔波恩特  距离2英里
圣路易斯  距离62英里
卡斯尔波恩特  那是你家乡是吧
Castle Point. That's your hometown right?
我的天  看看那风暴
Whoa. Look at that storm coming in.
好吧  你赢了
Okay, fine. You win.
欢迎来到卡斯尔波恩特
欢迎回家  罗伯塔
Welcome home, Roberta.
这么说这里你很熟了吗
So you know this town?
这是生我养我的地方
Born and raised here.
我们要避一避
We need to take cover.
附近有什么安全的地方吗
Is there someplace safe nearby?
有  我家有个防风窖
Yeah, there's a storm cellar in my house.
你家有多近
How close by is your house?
不远
It's not far.
我认识这些人
I knew these people.
有我的邻居
My neighbor.
我的老板
My boss.
我的...
My...
是他吗
Is that him?
他是谁
Who's him?
不是吧
Oh, no.
我们又不是来找你死掉的丈夫的
No. We are not here searching for dead hubby, are we?
我们走
Let's go.
避难所在这边
Shelter's this way.
走吧
Get going.
真绿啊
It's so green.
我从未见过这样的天空
I never seen a sky look like that.
我只在电视上看过龙卷风
I've only seen tornadoes on TV.
我不喜欢龙卷风
I don't like tornadoes.
我坚信它也不待见我
I'm pretty sure they don't like me either.
是你家吗
That it?
是的
That's it.
一万  过来
10K, come on!
来吧
Come on!
如果他在里面  他八成是...
If he's in there and he's...
我不会手下留情的
I will not hesitate.
甜蜜的僵尸啊
Home sweet zombie.
离开那把椅子
Get out of that chair!
起来  走开
Go on and get out of there!
这是我丈夫最喜爱的椅子
That's my husband's favorite chair!
好吧
All right.
楼上一切正常
Uh, upstairs is all good.
我来
I got this.
请不要开枪
Please don't shoot us.
我丈夫受伤了
My husband is hurt.
你们在我家做什么
What are you doing in my house?
一个消防员说我们在这会很安全
The fireman said we'd be safe here.
开始吧
Here we go.
像狗一样冲着我叫
Bark like a dog for me.
我不是在说你  但是我很感动
Well I wasn't talking to you, but I'm impressed.
天呐
God.
从三级风变成七层地狱了
From a Category Three to the Seventh Circle of Hell.
三角洲X光小队  希望你们不在这下方
Delta-Xray-Delta, I hope you guys aren't underneath that.
拜托  给我个信儿
Come on. Drop me a note.
发个信号弹  给我个电话
Send up a flare. Give me a ring.
找不到你们  我就帮不上忙
I can't help you if I can't find you.
你会没事的
You're going to be okay.
他是医生
He's a doctor.
我这医生也不过是徒有虚名而已
Well they sorta just call me Doc.
不要
No.
不用医生  我只是  需要睡一觉
No doctor. I just... need a nap.
老兄  那样可好不了
Oh that, no that wouldn't be good, dude.
别睡
Do not nap.
别让他睡过去  他至少是严重脑震荡
Don't let him fall asleep. He's got a bad concussion at least.
瑞克  瑞克
Rick? Rick?
救救他
Help him!
地下室是安全的
Basement's clear.
他会没事吧
Is he gonna be okay?
是这名消防员吗
Is this the fireman?
什么
What?
是这名消防员把你们带到这来的吗
Is this the fireman that brought you here?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许  他当时戴着头盔
Maybe. He was wearing a helmet.
也许是他
Maybe it's him.
我想是的
I think it is.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们得在风暴来袭之前离开这里
We need to get out of here before this storm hits.
你说去哪里
And go where, huh?
我们应该怎么做
What are we supposed to do,
就坐在这期待它错过这里吗
just sit here and hope it misses us?
地下室是安全的
The basement is secure.
我们可以待在下面安全度过
We can ride it out down there.
在它来袭之前我们先收集一些物资
Let's just gather some supplies before it hits.
厨房是个备货的好地方
Kitchen was pretty well stocked up.
那里有水和罐头食品
There's water and canned food.
但是  没有医疗用品  没有电池
No medical supplies, no batteries though.
我们得让通讯设备恢复使用
We need to get our communications up.
你们俩  去附近看看
You two, go out in the neighborhood.
看看能找到什么  但是别走远了
See what you can find. But don't go far.
确保在风暴来袭之前能够回来
Be sure to get back before the storm hits.
简妮  这些人在这里干什么
Janey what are all these people doing here?
我的父母随时都会回来吃晚饭
My parents will be home for dinner any minute.
他能挺得过来吗
Is he gonna make it?
你真的想知道吗
Is that a serious question?
我也不知道
I don't know.
他头部受伤了
He got cracked on the dome.
在他想吃大脑的时候
Okay, I for one do not
我不想和这个家伙
want to be trapped in a basement with this guy
一起被困在地下室里
when he starts craving brains.
别理他
Don't mind him.
他妈没教育好他
His mama didn't raise him right.
如果我有对症的药物或者急救箱
Well if I had the proper meds or a first aid kit...
消防站可能还有急救用品
You know the fire station may still have first aid supplies.
把地下室锁上
Hey, lock down the basement.
如果这个孩子变成了僵尸
If that kid turns,
我希望你能正确应对
I want you to be right on that.
好的  当然
Yeah, of course.
看着点摩菲
Keep an eye on Murphy.
在风暴开始前我们就会回来
We'll be back before the party starts.
艾迪
Addy!
什么
What?
怎么了
什么
What?
这地方唤起了我的好多回忆
This place brings back so many memories.
怎么了
What?!
我的初吻
My first kiss.
跟那个消防员吗
With the fireman?
是的  安托万
Antoine, yeah.
小心
Look out!
我都已经完全忘记那个吻了
I totally forgot about that kiss until now!
那个吻看来非比寻常
That must have been some kiss!
那可不仅仅只是个吻
It was more than just a kiss!
那个吻阐释了
It was a kiss that explained things
我们无法对彼此说出口的事
we couldn't seem to say to each other!
看看我们的大情圣
Look who's the big romantic!
我想这是你跟我说的第一件私事吧
I think that's the first personal story you ever told me!
我爱那个男孩
I loved that boy.
这边
This way.
看着好像很久没人来过了
Doesn't look like anybody's been here for a while.
对不起
Sorry.
看看有什么能用的然后走人
Let's find what we can and get out of here.
急救包看着不错
First aid kits look good.
没怎么用过
Hardly touched.
还有些吗啡
Even some morphine.
可别告诉多克
Don't tell Doc.
你知道  他可能还在这附近
You know he could still be around here somewhere.
两年前的新泽西之战我发了这张
I sent this after the Battle of New Jersey two years ago.
我们最亲近的一次告别
Closest we got to a goodbye.
我在他值班的时候被调走
I deployed while he was on duty.
我应该等他回家再走的
I should've waited for him to get home.
你看
Look.
有人住在你家
Someone's living in your house.
食品柜是满的
The pantry's stocked.
那小两口说他们见到一个消防员
That couple said they met a fireman.
有可能他还...
There's a chance he's...
那种生活已经过去了
That life is gone.
我早就意识到了这点
I've known that for a long time.
我们时间不多了
We don't have much time.
马上撤回避难所
Shelter! Now!
去还是留  做个选择吧
Pick your poison.
在这里比外面安全
It's safer in here than out there.
好的  你看到他了吗
Okay. Do you see him?
现在是活人对战死人
It's the living against the dead now.
好的
All right.
我没子弹了
I'm out.
我也是
Me too.
你后面
Behind you.
安托万
Antoine?
小心
Look out!
安托万
Antoine.
是他吗
Is that him?
不是
No.
不是  是他最好的朋友
No, it's his best friend,
迪尔伯恩
Dearborn.
马特·迪尔伯恩
Matt Dearborn.
给你
Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
小心点
Easy now.
抱歉
Sorry.
告诉外面那几个小伙子
Tell those frat boys out there
把死亡金属音乐关掉
to turn down the death metal.
不然我就再去报警
I'll call the cops again.
我会跟他们说的
I'll tell them.
这家伙因为血肿导致颅内压升高不堪负荷
The dude's brain is getting crushed by the swelling.
我们得降低颅内压
We need to relieve the pressure.
很好  那我们该怎么做
Great. How we gonna do that?
我并不是很清楚  不过
Uh, I don't know exactly. But...
以前在《急诊室的故事》看过一次处理方法
but I saw this once on an episode of ER.
我们得疏通血肿  应该是这样
We need to drain the blood out I think.
所以我需要有尖头又锋利的东西
So I need something sharp and pointy to...
比如螺丝锥或者碎冰锥一类的东西
like a corkscrew, an ice pick?
摩菲
Murphy!
摩菲  快来帮忙
Murphy? A little help.
妈的
Damn it.
摩菲
Murphy!
你在搞什么鬼
What the hell, man?
摩菲
Murphy!
我们这里都天下大乱了
The world's coming apart around us, man.
你还有心情去理了个发
And you decide it's time for a haircut?
别让他接近瑞克
Keep him away from Rick!
摩菲  我需要你来帮忙
Murphy, I need your help.
去找个锋利的东西来  我要刺穿他的头骨
Find something sharp to penetrate his skull.
要够锋利足以刺穿头骨  了解
Sharp enough to penetrate his skull. Got it.
是时候刺穿他了
About time we piked him.
他在说什么
What is he talking about?!
好好搜一下房间
Way to read the room!
他在说什么
What is he talking about?
别担心  没人要刺穿你丈夫
Don't, don't worry. Nobody's gonna pike your husband.
艾迪在哪里
Where's Addy?
艾迪
Addy!
艾迪  艾迪
Addy? Addy?
你怎么了
What, what is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
麦克  我需要你
Mack! I need you, man!
-去吧  -行
- Go. - All right.
找的怎么样了摩菲
How we doin' Murphy?!
多谢
Thanks.
好了
Okay.
按住他
Just hold him still.
听着  这方法要是奏效了可能会大出血
Now look, if this works right there could be a lot of blood.
但是出血是好滴
But that's good.
出血是应该滴
That's a good thing
因为我们要释放颅内压
because we want to relieve the pressure.
这样颅脑就会有空间
And then that way the brain will have room to...
你就别看了
Don't watch.
哎呦我擦
Oh damn.
这都是哥预料之中的事儿
I knew this was gonna happen.
别看我啊  大夫
Don't look at me... doctor.
天哪  小子
Jeez, kid.
我拿来当锤子的哈  锤子
As a hammer. A hammer.
好主意好主意
That's good.
嗷  神呐
Oh God.
看来压力降下来了
Well I guess that relieved the pressure.
这办法有用吗
Is this gonna work?
鬼知道啊
I don't know.
那一集结尾我又没看好吗
I didn't see the end of the episode.
他会好起来的  我相信
He's gonna be all right. I know it.
一定会的
I know it.
快  轻轻压住止血
Here. Just apply pressure.
像这样
Just like that.
特洛伊
Troy.
文斯
Vince.
迈克
Mike.
还有迪尔伯恩
And Dearborn.
我仁慈地结束了你们的生命
I give you mercy.
愿上帝赐予你们安宁祥和
May God give you peace.
准备好了吗
You ready?
来对付外面的吧
Let's take it to 'em.
僵尸都跑哪儿去了
Where'd they all go?
算了  走吧
Come on. Let's go.
不错啊
That's good.
这是好兆头啊
也许我们应该趁着他昏迷的时候
Maybe I should've pulled the drill bit
把钻头给拔出来
while he was still knocked out.
罗伯塔
Roberta!
你不觉得那东西很疯狂吗
Does that thing look mad to you?
那个该不会是...
Is that what I think?
不是鲨鱼哟
They ain't sharks!
神啊  你认真的吗  认真的吗
Really, God?! Really?!
快  我们得赶紧进去
Come on! We got to get inside!
快点  没时间了
Come on! There's no time!
走吧
Let's go!
摩菲  你去对付那只僵尸
Murphy, take care of that zombie!
知道了  多克
Get it, Doc!
他怎么样了
How is he?
我不知道
I don't know.
你做了什么
What did you do?
给他做了颅骨减压术
Oh, decompressive craniectomy.
我拿电钻钻了他的头骨
I put a drill to the dome.
一万和卡桑德拉去哪儿了
Where's 10K and Cassandra?
我不知道
I don't know.
沃伦
Warren!
摩菲  你在干什么
Murphy! What are you doing?!
捅死那玩意儿  快点
Pike that thing now!
我们回不去了  找个地方躲起来
We're not gonna make it back! Take shelter!
去车上
Run for the car!
罗伯塔
Roberta!
罗伯塔  你在干什么
Roberta! What are you doing?!
罗伯塔  听到了吗
Roberta! Can you hear me?!
请别这样
Please don't do this!
罗伯塔与安托万
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
暴风随时会来
The storm's gonna come any second!
拜托  快出来
Come on! Hurry up!
拜托罗伯塔
Come on, Roberta!
罗伯塔  你在干什么  罗伯塔
Roberta! What are you doing, Roberta?!
开门
Open the door!
马克  帮我把他搬到桌子下面  好吗
Mack, help me get him under the table, will ya?
好
Okay.
我来倒数
On my count.
少整没用得了
Shut up, Doc.
拿上毯子
Get the blankets.
罗伯塔  听得到吗
Roberta! Can you hear me?!
这次我必须等他  查理
I have to wait for him this time, Charlie.
我欠他太多了
I owe him that much.
不  不  该死  马上下楼
No. No! Goddamn it! Come down right now!
楼上不安全
It is not safe up here!
就像你说的
It's like you said.
我无法忘却
I can't start forgetting...
直到我知道一切
until I know.
查理  求你别这样
Roberta, please don't do this.
好啦  这就好了啦
Got it. That's it!
沃伦呢
Where's Warren?
她不肯下来
She's not coming.
什么
What?
她不下来
She's not coming?
她留在外面会死的
She's gonna get killed out there.
她必须下来
She's got to get down here.
她不肯下来
She's not coming.
摩菲
Murphy.
你开什么玩笑
You kidding me?
别胡闹了
Quit screwing around with this thing.
慈悲
Mercy.
好
Okay.
坚持住
Hang on.
不  不
Oh no! Oh no!
天啊
Oh God.
我在等着你
I waited for you.
还挺好玩的
Well that was fun.
沃伦
Warren.
你脸色不好  老大
You don't look so good, chief.
我要出去
I need to get out of here.
我要离开这
I need to get out of here now.
罗伯塔
Roberta!
查理
Hi, Charlie.
你怎么没被...
Why didn't you...
你是怎么...
How did you...
我一直想回家
I tried to go home.
真的
I did.
但我还好好地在这里
But I'm still here.
谢天谢地你还在
Thank God you are.
我还在
I'm still here.
你太疯狂了
You're crazy.
你知道你自己很疯狂  对吧
You're crazy. You know that, right?
略知一二吧
A little bit, yeah.
沃伦
Warren.
谢谢你
Thank you.
如果哥看到一个小矮人  哥会吓死的
Man... If I see a munchkin, I'm gonna freak.
我需要立马出发
I need to go!
我不太喜欢你现在的造型
I'm not sure if I care for that look.
又没人问你的意见
Nobody asked you.
发型易改
New haircut.
本性难移
Same Murphy.
多克  谢谢你
Hey, Doc. Thanks.
真的很感谢你
Thank you, truly.
你有没有可以止痛的药
Do you have anything for the pain?
哦  我...
Oh, I...
很抱歉
I am so sorry.
要是有就好了
I wish I did.
好吧好吧
Oh, hell.
给你啦
Here.
悠着点吃
Take it easy on those.
这些可都是好东西呢
That's good stuff.
你们俩会没事吧
Are you folks gonna be all right?
瑞克的家人就在附近
Rick's got family nearby.
我们还要继续寻找他们
We're gonna keep looking for them.
不过  谢谢你们
But thanks.
谢谢你们所做的一切
Thanks for everything.
怎么了
What?
你说的没错
You were right.
我确实得回来
I did need to come back.
当时我都没搞清楚安托万身上发生了什么
Even if I never know for sure what happened to Antoine,
就跟大家道别
I said my goodbye.
我知道现在我人在这里  我很好
I know I'm okay with being here now.
和你在一起
With you.
我也很高兴
And I'm good with that too.
我一直都想这样做
I always wanted to do that.
我能感觉得到
I could tell.
世间的幸存者们  大家好
Survivors of the world, hello.
如果你们还能听到我说话  恭喜你们
If you're hearing this, congrats.
说明你们还活着
You're still alive.
你们真是人渣中的极品
You are the baddest of the badasses.
你们害怕的既不是人类
Fearing neither man
不是龙卷风  也不是僵尸
nor twister nor living dead.
我要关掉耳麦了
My headset is off to you.